Alright in this clip we're going to be drawing the kings robe.
I would say for this one, go ahead and put away the old fine tip pen, and break out, if you have one, something a little bit thicker.
I use the Rectractable Sharpie for these types of things.
And we're not going to draw anything too crazy, nothing flowing really.
Kind of come down, like so.
We'll make it, comes all the way to the ground like that, along this side, really sort of call attention to it, like right there.
Now if we want to, we can go in here and like create sort of a shadow, like between- create a really big difference, between the robe and the outer part of his clothes, we can do that if we wanted to.
I won't go into too much detail there, you kind of see what the possibilities are, as far as that's concerned.
And what we'll do actually, we'll make this robe sort of coming out to the side like this.
So, now we'll get the other pen again, something a little less bold.
We'll come in here and add some details.
Now make that robe flow a bit.
Just add a few flowing lines.
Move over here, do the same and come up like this, some real little flowing lines, just like that, to really just add character to the robe, like that.
That's looking interesting.
Like that.
Okay, that robe is looking pretty good I think.
So, we've pretty much got the whole outfit done now for our king.
And what we'll do in the last and final step is kind of go over this from head to toe and add the details that help really sell the picture.
So, if you're all done with the robe, let's go ahead and move on to the last little clip for the king.